KARTHIKEYAN V

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

9944658008, 8072217943

vijayakarthik13@gmail.com

COIMBATORE

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstarp
- React JS (Basic)
- JQuery
- PHP
- Codelgniter
- Laravel
- MYSQL
- Photoshop
- Figma

EDUCATION

MBA (Finance & Human Resources)
KSRangasamy College of Technology
- Tirchegode

Tirchegode

Jun 2015 – Jul 2017

BA (English Literature)
KSR College of Arts and Science

- Tirchegode

Jun 2012 - Aug 2015

AREA OF INTEREST

- · Web Designing
- · Web Development
- CMS Development
- · Responsive Design

PROFILE

A broad-skilled professional with an experience of 3+ years in Web Developer. A key component of my success lies in the fact that I never limit myself to a particular technology as a web development skill and hence. I've always embraced new technologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

BLAZON TECHNOLOGY - COIMBATORE

May 2023 - Aug 2024

I am a web developer with 1 year and 1 month of experience specializing in frontend technologies and UI design. I am proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, jQuery, Figma, and, Photoshop. I have strong visualization skills and a thorough understanding of client requirements, allowing me to deliver high-quality results. I am focused on completing deliverables on time with a high-priority

WEB DESIGNER

BANYAN INFOTECH - COIMBATORE

Sep 2021 - Feb 2023

A web developer with 1 year and 4 months of experience in software development, including **HTML**, **CSS**, **JavaScript**, and **PHP** (**CodeIgniter**). Proficient in using prototype tools such as Photoshop, with strong visualization skills and good knowledge of usability. I assure you that business requirements and functional specifications for the module are tested and fulfilled before the code is delivered for integration.

WEB DEVELOPER

ZAVIEN SOLUTION - COIMBATORE

May 2020 - Jul 2021

Web Developer with 1 year and 2 months of experience in software development, including proficiency in **HTML**, **CSS**, **JavaScript**, and **PHP** (**Laravel**). Possesses strong visualization skills and a solid understanding of usability. Experienced in collaborating with clients and technical teams to successfully execute projects. A skilled team member with a proven ability to maximize productivity.

PROJECTS

GR PROMOTERS

https://grpromoters.com/

• SIGNATURE INTERIORS

https://www.signatureinteriors.in/

• GOWRI PLATES: BUFFET PLATES

https://www.gowriplates.com/

PRESSO

https://www.raretexfashions.com/

RARE TEX FASHIONPMG SCHOOL

https://www.pmgschool.com/

GREEN LIGHT INTERNATIONAL

https://www.gli-oman.com/

• DR. MM. YUSUF

http://www.drmmyusuf.com/